const quizData = [
    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: '"false"',
    //     b: '1',
    //     c: 'true',
    //     d: '0',
    //     correct: 'a',
    //     id: '1',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Какое значение будет в result?',
    //     a: 'null',
    //     b: '2',
    //     c: '3',
    //     d: 'undefined',
    //     correct: 'd',
    //     id: '2',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Какое значение будет в result?',
    //     a: 'boolean',
    //     b: 'null',
    //     c: 'undefined',
    //     d: '0',
    //     correct: 'a',
    //     id: '3',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: 'false',
    //     b: '"Аниме"',
    //     c: '0',
    //     d: '1',
    //     correct: 'b',
    //     id: '4',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Какое значение будет в result?',
    //     a: 'null',
    //     b: '1',
    //     c: '2',
    //     d: 'SyntaxError',
    //     correct: 'c',
    //     id: '5',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Чему будет равно n?',
    //     a: '8',
    //     b: '6',
    //     c: '7',
    //     d: '9',
    //     correct: 'a',
    //     id: '6',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: '2',
    //     b: 'undefined',
    //     c: '1',
    //     d: 'null',
    //     correct: 'c',
    //     id: '7',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: '10',
    //     b: 'SyntaxError',
    //     c: 'undefined',
    //     d: '25',
    //     correct: 'a',
    //     id: '8',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: '5',
    //     b: 'undefined',
    //     c: 'null',
    //     d: 'ReferenceError',
    //     correct: 'd',
    //     id: '9',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Чему будет равно n?',
    //     a: '8',
    //     b: '7',
    //     c: '1',
    //     d: '4',
    //     correct: 'b',
    //     id: '10',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: 'number',
    //     b: 'boolean',
    //     c: 'string',
    //     d: '5',
    //     correct: 'c',
    //     id: '11',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: 'false',
    //     b: 'boolean',
    //     c: 'true',
    //     d: '"10"',
    //     correct: 'a',
    //     id: '12',
    // },

    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: '12',
    //     b: '10',
    //     c: '9',
    //     d: '11',
    //     correct: 'd',
    //     id: '13',
    // },


    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: '1 2 3 4 5',
    //     b: '0 1 2 3 4',
    //     c: 'undefined',
    //     d: 'TypeError',
    //     correct: 'b',
    //     id: '14',
    // },


    // {
    //     question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
    //     a: '10 14 18',
    //     b: 'a b c',
    //     c: 'TypeError',
    //     d: 'null',
    //     correct: 'c',
    //     id: '15',
    // },


    {
        question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
        a: 'TypeError',
        b: 'undefined',
        c: '4',
        d: 'ReferenceError',
        correct: 'c',
        id: '16',
    }, 


    {
        question: 'Какое значение будет в res?',
        a: 'undefined',
        b: 'null',
        c: '"0"',
        d: 'object',
        correct: 'd',
        id: '17',
    },

    {
        question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
        a: '6 1 3',
        b: 'null',
        c: 'ReferenceError',
        d: 'undefined',
        correct: 'a',
        id: '18',
    },
    {
        question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
        a: '5',
        b: '10',
        c: 'undefined',
        d: '1',
        correct: 'b',
        id: '19',
    },

    {
        question: 'Что выведет в консоль?',
        a: 'NaN',
        b: '9',
        c: '0',
        d: 'TypeError',
        correct: 'b',
        id: '20',
    },
];


export default quizData;



